# JESSIE COLEMAN

Decatur GA · (915) 867 0700 Jessiecoleman928@gmail.com

Third year student at Emory University. Experienced with working under fast-paced environment, as well as OOP programming, website design, app design, and game development. Currently creating a website and learning CSS/HTML/JavaScript.

## **EXPERIENCE**

**AUG 2022 - PRESENT** 

#### **EMORY COMPUTER SCIENCE LAB STAFF**

My responsibilities include tutoring computer science students, computer repair, and computer maintenance.

MAY 2022 - AUG 2022

#### **BEST BUY COMPUTER REPAIR**

My job was to diagnose and fix software/hardware problems with clients' computers, as well as smartphones and tablets.

## **EDUCATION**

**MAY 2019** 

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA, FRANKLIN HIGH SCHOOL

JUNE 2020-PRESENT

**COMPUTER SCIENCE, EMORY UNIVERSITY** 

## SKILLS

- Java/C#/C
- HTML/CSS/JavaScript

- Python/Lua
- Unity/Android Studio/Arduino

## **PROJECTS**

- Created online multiplayer tank game https://sacredstudios.itch.io/chidi-tanks-03-alpha
- Created visualization of A\* pathfinding algorithm using Arduino.
- Created website using CSS/JavaScript/HTML.
- Created map/sprites for 2D game with Unity
- Created simple clicker game using Lua.
- Created animated poster using Android Studio.